

Teixeira

React Developer

Portfolio: dantxal.com

github.com/dantxal

dantxal@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/daniel-txal

About me

Hello, I am Daniel Teixeira, 26-years old, Full Stack developer, I'm very tech-savvy and a React enthusiast.

I started studying React in the first-half of 2019, and have been working and studying it together with NodeJS and React Native.

I like to keep myself updated with new technologies and metodologies in this spectrum.

am proficient in spoken and written English.

Professional Experience

Full Stack Developer

Full Time

Snapboard Inc. PRemote

Oct, 2019 - Aug, 2020

Product design, implementing integrations, creating components, e2e testing. Typescript, React, NodeJS, Cypress.io, Passport

React Developer

Freelance

Freelancing

Remote

Jun, 2019 - Oct, 2019

Comissioned apps for local businesses. React, Electron

Education

React Tech Stack - Bootcamp

Aug, 2019 - Oct, 2019 Rocketseat

Imersive course on the React, Node and React Native ecosystem. Many practical exercises, developed entire apps with databases, back-end, front-end and mobile.

The course also included:

- DevOps with docker, mongodb, postgres;
- Advanced styling using styled-components library;
- State management with Redux and Redux-Saga;
- Tests with Jest.

Javascript and React Courses

Apr, 2019 - May, 2019

codewithmosh.com

Introductory course to Javascript ES6, and React. During the course I developed an entire Video Rental app with a fake API.

English Course

Jan, 2007 - Dec, 2011



A 5-years long course with both written and oral tests every semester. The course aims at teaching students everything they might need if they ever decide to study/work in a English-speaking country.